{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_12_09UGQ6",
                "player_6_09UGQ6",
                "player_16_09UGQ6"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                12,
                6,
                16
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "crouch",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair.",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black fedora, black turtleneck, black pants, and black shoes."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    7.29,
                    -4541.633,
                    82.097,
                    0,
                    -83.49527471799455,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    110.798,
                    -4648.013,
                    82.097,
                    0,
                    98.23684741703335,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    26.869,
                    -4764.038,
                    82.097,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -214.003,
            -4843.838,
            82.097
        ],
        "sample_radius": 579.266555638643
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            12.766,
            -5084.556,
            81.969,
            0,
            85.30959371244057,
            0
        ],
        [
            -257.253,
            -4463.976,
            82.328,
            0,
            -31.499623439961873,
            0
        ],
        [
            377.668,
            -4829.64,
            82.097,
            0,
            151.5551043034754,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a crouched position in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many figures are lying motionless on the ground?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many individuals are engaged in holding something?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many men are observed among the figures?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene are bald?",
                "answer": "zero"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many figures are both hat-clad and carrying a dark bag?",
                "answer": "one"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the gray suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "C. liedown"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man wearing a fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. running",
                    "C. holding_something",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "C. holding_something"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the front of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the back of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the front of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            }
        }
    }
}